but so for most people the idea of
having the luxury of trying to make
sense of the world is something they
don't even feel like they have because
their nose down just trying to like do
the next couple things they have to do
and then other people who are actually
trying to get ahead are optimizing for
simulations and distortion bubbles
rather than trying to make sense of the
world so there's a lot of people who
aren't actually even trying to make
sense of the world now when I asked what
is meaningful what is meaningful is
going to be bound to what I think is
real
and if I give up on knowing what is real
there's a way in which I'm giving up on
the depth of my connectedness to what's
meaningful
so yes giving up on sense making there's
a is kind of an expression of a type of
nihilism and it and it feeds into
further nihilism